ICICI Lombard is known for its wife's
death which makes the processes
like booking a two wheeler third party policy
very easy.
Welcome to this video in which we will
tell you about the steps for booking a two wheeler third party policy.
Come to the Digital Seva Portal home page and
click on the Insurance option. Type ICICI Lombard in the search option.
Click on the ICICI Lombard icon. You will be redirected to the Partner
Home Page i.e. ICICI
Lombard Home Page. On the right side of the home page
you will find our product options. How to
buy a two wheeler third party bike policy.
Click on the WTP icon.
Click on Renew Existing and Lapsed Policies and then click on the Get Full Quota tab.
Thank you.
This screen shows Registration Details.
After coming to the WTP page,
enter your customer's vehicle registration number
and
click on Get It on top to get the complete vehicle details. Check the
model, manufacturing, engine and
chassis number with your RC on the page. From the
screen you will see those details. Get the cover at the
premium rate as per your requirement.  has been deleted and TPD
is restricted up to 6000 Previous
policy details have already been entered Click on No option Click on
orange gate tap to view premium Rs 828 Click on
blue create new customer tap to enter customer details on your screen Enter customer
name, address, pin code, email ID and
phone number After entering customer details, click on orange gate tap
to view proposal number generated with premium Rs 828 At the
bottom right corner of the page, you will find Buy Policy option in blue color
Click on it to go to CSC Wallet payment page
View screen for policy PDF After
entering your CSC password and wallet PIC,
wait for some time
you will reach a page where you will
see your policy number and
an option to view your customer's policy PDF